Notice.
Notice
I have compiled the current state
of affairs as concisely as possible.
Play compilation?
Understood
Understood.
Beginning playback.
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Slime Diaries
The Events Thus Far
Encounter with the individual
called Gazel, king of Dwargon.
Founding of Master's nation,
the Jura Tempest Federation.
Founding of the Nation
Establishment of diplomatic relations
between the Armed Nation of Dwargon
and the Jura Tempest Federation.
Special mention
Special mention.
Nice to meet you!
I'm Milim Nava!
A Demon Lord, the individual
called Milim Nava, attacks.
Attack
I've arrived!
The Tempest Federation falls.
Fall
You're all going to serve
the Demon Lord Milim Nava!
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Slime Diaries
Milim           Diaries
Milim Diaries!
Day 7: Here Comes the Demon Lord!
She fell asleep after eating her fill.
Let's get her back.
Uh, hey...
Milim!
I wanna be a Demon Lord, too!
Take me as your pupil!
Very well.
You are my bestie, after all.
Yay! I love you, Milim!
Just when it was getting good...
Where'd everyone go?
In there, huh?
Therefore, I believe the one best
suited to be in charge of Lady Milim
is her bestie, Great Rimuru.
Eep!
I agree.
I also agree.
Agreed!
Agreed.
W-Wait a minute!
The majority agrees, so it's settled.
Which means Great Rimuru will henceforth
be in charge of Lady Milim.
Rimuru!
Did you decide you want
to be a Demon Lord yet?!
Great Rimuru!
Look what's happened to you!
H-He won't come off!
Sorry, Milim, but I'm really busy
building a nation right now.
My body is having a tough
time right now, too.
Besides, a Demon Lord?
Wouldn't that just bring me
more enemies and obligations?
What?! Not at all!
I mean, Demon Lords... um, uh...
They can shout out whatever random
attack names they come up with,
and everyone will just go along with it!
Because they're Demon Lords!
Wait, wait! No, no, no, no!
Well, what now? You made the mood all weird.
It's not my fault.
Rimuru! That sound means it's time for lunch!
I know, I know.
But you don't even need to eat food, do you?
The food here is yummy,
so I can eat it over and over!
Then, I'll bring you some.
I'm finished.
Lady Milim, be sure to
eat your vegetables, too.
These are just straight-up carrots!
But they're properly cooked.
They're sweet and delicious.
No!
Carrots smell gross! I can't stand them!
Picky eaters don't grow up big and strong.
That's fine!
You can still become a Demon
Lord without eating carrots!
Look!
I cut them into all kinds of shapes!
Hey, these are cute.
Yummy!
I could eat tons of them
if they're like this!
Just eat already.
That was so good.
The weather's nice today,
so I'm gonna go explore the town!
Oh, that sounds lovely.
I'll make some snacks,
so please come by again later.
Snacks?!
Awesome! I can't wait!
But first, you have a town to explore, right?
Oh, yeah!
I'll be back!
I'll play with you, Ranga!
It seems I have no choice in the matter.
But I am Great Rimuru's—
Don't be shy, now.
I love pets.
O-Okay...
I don't remember it well,
but I think I petted one
like this a long time ago.
Please... As I was just
saying, I'm waiting for—
Wh-What masterful fingers...
She really is a Demon Lord!
Is this the spot? Right here?
There! There ya go!
Ranga... You like it right here?
I'm going to be swept away!
I'll drown!
There! There! There ya go!
Great Rimuru!
I see you've been unfaithful.
Well, well...
I'll have to tell Great Rimuru about this.
Hup!
So fluffy!
What the heck happened?
Did Gobta do something?
Hey!
Why is that the first thing you say?!
Ooh, you're tougher than I thought.
I just wanted to help you, Lady Milim!
Lady Milim! That outfit looks great on you!
That other one was made for someone
a bit more voluptuous, y'know?
I only spoke for all of us
in giving you some gentlemanly advi—
Is that true?
Oh, I gotta get back to Shuna's place!
Those snacks should be ready by now!
Snacks!
Oh!
Welcome back, Lady Milim.
Snacks! Snacks! Snacks!
Yes, here you go.
Corn Steamed Buns
Yay!
These are tasty, too!
Barley
Tea
Just make yourself at home.
Slime Diaries.
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Slime Diaries
Carrots...
Carrots... Raw carrots are gross...
Middray, make sure they're cooked...
I'm impressed you can just
order Milim around like that.
Like telling her to eat her carrots.
She is a Demon Lord, you know.
And a dangerous one...
Calamity Class
It's rude to talk about her like that.
It's true that Lady Milim can be reckless,
but she's sensible enough to understand
reason if you just talk to her.
That's why you became her
friend, too, isn't it?
Well, I guess you're not wrong.
She understood things surprisingly well.
Yes.
I've spent my life watching someone reckless,
who never thought anything through,
so I can tell.
Wow, really?
I guess you've had it pretty
tough, Princess Shuna.
Yep
Yes, true.
So what's up?
The truth is... I don't find
Lady Milim very agreeable.
This isn't like you.
Are you still bitter because she
clobbered you when you first met?
If only I'd had more power back then...
You would not have to trouble
yourself with what Lady Milim does.
Shion...
You were that concerned about me?
Well, after all...
The only woman who should be
allowed to trouble you is me!
I won't let anyone else have this role!
Are you listening?!
Great Rimuru!
Please let me in!
What kind of face are you making right now?
Great Rimuru!
We meet again, Dragonewt... uh...
H-Hello, Lady Milim!
Gabiru, wasn't it?
Isn't that amazing? I remember you!
Wha... What?! You remember my name?!
I love interesting people like you!
Interesting
Tough People
That's our Sir Gabiru!
You're a big deal!
Indeed!
Gabiru! Gabiru! Gabiru!
Aw...
It must be my virtuous nature
and the sweet musk I give off.
Just kidding!
I sense...
a mysterious connection between us.
Perhaps we are fated...
or ill-fated, as it were.
You haven't...
professed yourself a Hero, have you?
Step right up! Come one, come all!
See a battle to the death between
the hero Gabiru and Death Panda!
Hero Gabiru VS Death Panda
Hero Gabiru
is as shocked as you are
Oh!
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Slime Diaries!
Slime Diaries
Hey, that's one of Clayman's...
Sir Gabiru!
My wings won't come out! I'm too panicked!
This way!
Good gracious!
Gah, the sunlight!
You are essentially the
Orc Lord, are you not?
Why live such a mundane life
when you have so much power?
Do you not wish to display
your might through force?
Is it so entertaining to carry rocks around?
There is value in building
something to leave behind.
We got lots again today!
Yeah. Let's head home.
Mom's waiting.
Yeah!
This is...
the task that has been bestowed upon me.
Hmm...
I don't understand.
Mind if I watch for a bit longer?
Feel free.
Great Rimuru, do you have a moment?
Sure.
What's up?
Well...
I would like to report the damages
caused by Lady Milim thus far.
Rigurd... are you angry?
No, no. Certainly not.
Doorknobs, window glass,
eating utensils, etc...
W-Well, for a Catastrophe,
these are pretty minor damages...
Actually, those are only from this morning.
This is...
the report of damages done this afternoon.
Huh?
Uh, Rigurd... are you angry?
Certainly not.
Damage Report
Assembly Building  Doors: more added for a total of 5
The number of doors is up to five,
Damage Report
Central Avenue  Shops: 2 half-destroyed
two shops on Central Avenue
are half-destroyed,
Damage Report
Central Avenue  Statue commemorating nation's founding: destroyed
and the statue commemorating
the founding is destroyed.
But we just put that up...
What?! Snack Bar Jura's sign?!
O-Okay, I get it! I'll talk to her!
As the representative of this
nation and as her friend,
I'll be tough on her!
And this damage report just came to me.
Additional Damages
Rigurd... are you angry?
Certainly not.
Milim, I need more nails.
Jeez, she fell asleep again?
Some Demon Lord.
She's worn out after so much excitement.
She saw many new things and
met many new people today.
What is she, a child?
Let her be a child.
The key to living a long life
is to stay young at heart.
She lives free, lets her emotions
run wild, and hates boredom.
You enjoy that type of lifestyle, do you not?
Yeah, but I'm the leader of a nation now.
Responsibility comes before freedom.
You have matured so much, Great Rimuru.
In that case...
I hope you will do the responsible
thing and fix my sign.
But I wasn't the one who—
You are the leader and the one
in charge of Lady Milim, yes?
Great Rimuru!
You can do it!
Oh, all right. Guess I'll do it.
Yay!
Snack Bar Jura.
Jura
That's not the title!
Hey, you're drooling.
Inside Rimuru's Stomach
This is a sight I never thought I'd see.
Lady Milim certainly is
quite the free spirit.
Imagine falling asleep and being
carried home on piggyback...
So even you, as a fellow Catastrophe,
frown upon her foolish behavior?
Of course I do!
If I weren't trapped in here,
I would rip her off of
him and smack her awake,
then I'd bring down my
fist as I lectured her!
"That's supposed to be my place!"
...is what I'd say.
You want... to be carried piggyback?
It's a heartwarming display
of friendship, is it not?
It's surreal.
Also, you'd crush him.
Rimuru, you love this nation that much?
Oh, you heard us?
Well, I did build this
nation from the ground up.
All the people in this town
are precious to me, too.
Aren't you scared?
To have so many people who
are precious to you...
If even one of those bonds were to be lost...
I'd be scared.
The most precious things are
always small and far too fragile.
You will regret it.
You'll regret building all this.
And when that time comes,
you won't be yourself anymore.
Go back to sleep.
Just sleep.
The next morning,
Milim wasn't in the guest room.
The only thing we found was a silence that made
everything up to yesterday seem like a lie.
I'd be scared.
Yeah?
She might never come back here...
I'm back!
Want some, Rimuru?
They're freshly picked!
Where'd you get those?!
I got them for fixing the
fence around the farm!
I said I was sorry, too!
After all that talk about losing
bonds and precious things?!
Huh? What are you talking about?
I can't wait to see what fun
things will happen today!
Great Rimuru!
Looks like this storm isn't over yet.
Preview
Rigurd... are you angry?
Certainly not.
Next time, "A Fruitful Autumn."
Rigurd, you are angry, aren't you?!